<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <template id="bear_content">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <section class="s_text_image pt32 pb32" data-name="Image - Text">
                    <div class="container">
                        <a href="/">
                            <strong>Back to home</strong>
                        </a>
                        <div class="row align-items-center">
                            <img src='/climate_website/static/src/img/bear.png' alt="Placeholder"
                                 style="margin-left: 16%;height: 500px;"/>
                            <div class="row">

                                <div class="col-12" style="padding-left: 10%;font-size: 19px;line-height: 30px;">
                                    <br></br>
                                    Polar bears (Ursus maritimus) are the poster child for the impacts of climate change
                                    on species, and justifiably so.
                                    To date, global warming has been most pronounced in the Arctic, and this trend is
                                    projected to continue.
                                    There are suggestions that before mid-century we could have a nearly ice-free Arctic
                                    in the summer.
                                    This increases the urgency with which we must act to reduce our greenhouse gas
                                    emissions to delay or avoid some of the worst consequences of climate change.
                                    <br></br>
                                </div>

                                <div class="col-12" style="padding-left: 10%;font-size: 19px;line-height: 30px;">
                                    Polar bears have relatively high genetic diversity within the species and can
                                    disperse over very long distances, suggesting that
                                    they may have some capacity to adapt to the ongoing changes in the Arctic.
                                    <br></br>
                                </div>

                                <div class="col-12" style="padding-left: 10%;font-size: 19px;line-height: 30px;">
                                    However, their dependence on sea ice makes them highly vulnerable to a changing
                                    climate. Polar bears rely heavily on the sea ice
                                    environment for traveling, hunting, mating, resting, and in some areas, maternal
                                    dens. In particular, they depend heavily on sea ice-dependent
                                    prey, such as ringed and bearded seals. Additionally, their long generation time and
                                    low reproductive rate may limit their ability to adapt to
                                    changes in the environment.
                                    <br></br>
                                </div>

                                <div class="col-12" style="padding-left: 10%;font-size: 19px;line-height: 30px;">
                                    Priorities for climate-informed polar bear conservation should include identifying
                                    and protecting the “last ice areas,” the parts of the Arctic
                                    that are projected to retain sea ice farthest into the future. It is also important
                                    to increase monitoring of polar bear populations, particularly
                                    their responses to declining sea ice. And as polar bears spend more time on land, we
                                    need to be prepared to manage for increased human-polar bear conflict.
                                    <br></br>
                                </div>

                            </div>
                            <!--                            <a href="/">Back to home</a>-->
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </section>
            </t>
        </template>
    </data>
</odoo>